var data = [{
	"question": "What historic city is located between two seas and is split between two continents?",
	"correctAnswer": "Istanbul",
	"question_id": 1,
	"category":"city"
}, {
	"question": "What is the most populated urban place?",
	"correctAnswer": "Tokyo",
	"question_id": 2,
	"category":"city"
}, {
	"question":"Most of the population within the limits of this major American city live on islands. Where is this city?",
	"correctAnswer":"New York",
	"question_id":3,
	"category":"city"
}, {
	"question":"What is the most populated city in South America?",
	"correctAnswer":"Sao Paulo",
	"question_id":4,
	"category":"city"
}, {
	"question":"Home of the famous Eifel Tower?",
	"correctAnswer":"Paris",
	"question_id":5,
	"category":"city"
}, {
	"question":"Which Asian city is also an independent nation?",
	"correctAnswer":"Singapore",
	"question_id":6,
	"category":"city"
}, {
	"question":"Which city in the world has the most bridges?",
	"correctAnswer":"Hamburg",
	"question_id":7,
	"category":"city"
}, {
	"question":"Which city was built on 7 hills?",
	"correctAnswer":"Rome",
	"question_id":8,
	"category":"city"
}, {
	"question":"What is the capital city of Litvania?",
	"correctAnswer":"Vilnius",
	"question_id":9,
	"category":"city"
}, {
	"question":"Which city is famous for one of the Seven Wonders of the World and its Great Library in ancient times?",
	"correctAnswer":"Alexandria",
	"question_id":10,
	"category":"city"
}

]

/*{
"1":
	{
		"question" : ["What historic city is located between two seas and is split between two continents?"],
		"correcAnswer" : ["Istanbul"]
	}
}*/
/*
"2"	
	{
		question: "What is the most populated urban place?",
		correcAnswer: "Tokio"
	},
"3"	
	{
		question: "Most of the population within the limits of this major American city live on islands. Where is this city?",
		correcAnswer: "New York"
	},
"4"
	{
		question: "Which river crosses the equator twice? ",
		correcAnswer: "Congo"
	},
"5"
	
	{
		question: "In which country is ice hockey the national sport?",
		correcAnswer: "Canada"
	},
"6"
	{
		question: "What is the most populated part of the world?  ",
		correcAnswer: "Europe"
	},
}*/